

JUVY ANN MONIS LIGASAN

Captain Waitress

PROFILE

Seven years' experience in F & B in banquet department. Searching for an opportunity that will allow the use and development of my professional skills and abilities. I have extraordinary knowledge and background in the restaurant that would be beneficial to the position offered.

CONTACT

PHONE:

+965 66520081

Whatsapp No.

+639281534432

ADRESS:

Bldg. 7283 Beirut Street Hawally

Kuwait

EMAIL:

monisligasan@gmail.com

EDUCATION

Our Lady of Fatima University Philippines 2002- 2003

Undergraduate of BS Hotel and Restaurant Management

Asia Pacific Caregiver and Healthcare Training Center, Inc. February 10, 2020 – December 17, 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Room Service Dar Al Shifa Hospital Tarig Alghanim Support and Catering Services July 2022 – till date

- Assisting the dietician preparing meals for patients in accordance with set menus and portion standards.
- Delivering trays and dishes at designated rooms and times.
- Setting, clearing, and sanitizing over bed tables.
- Following established safety for all food and equipment.

Captain Waitress in Emirates Palace August 2019 – August 2020 December 2011- April 2018

- Supervise and assist the smooth operation and running of the service.
- Direct and supervise the service staff during the service and to ensure all duties are performed to the required standards.
- Extend prompt service to all guests.
- Ensure proper organization, planning and control of china, silver, linen, glassware, menus, and other supplies.

Food Attendant Al Diar Capital Hotel in Abu Dhabi June 2008 – May 2010

- Greet and welcome the guest.
- Assisting the guests for their inquiries and needs.
- Take order and serving them carefully
- Settling the bill of the guest with customer care.
- Maintaining the cleanliness of the store.

CERTIFICATES & ACHIEVEMENTS

- AWARDED AS EMPLOYEE OF THE MONTH.
- EMIRATES PALACE HOTEL
- AL DIAR CAPITAL HOTEL (YEAR 2009)
- SUCCESSFULLY COMPLETED THE EFST PROGRAM (ESSENTIAL FOOD SAFETY TRAINING)
- COMPLAINT HANDLING PROGRAM
- TELEPHONE ETIQUETTE
- GUEST SERVICE
- GROOMING STANDARD
- F&B UP-SELLING
- FIRE AND SAFETY TRAINING FIRST AID TRAINING.